

Contact

551-998-7611

■ homesbygabby@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/gabrielaespinal

www.homesbygabbie.com

Skills

Yardi
Sales
Marketing
Real Estate
MS Outlook
MS Word
MS Excel

Certifications

Indeed

Computer Skills: PC Expert

Real Estate Proficient

Customer Focus & Orientation

Highly Proficient

LinkedIn

Microsoft Excel Microsoft Word Microsoft Outlook

About me



Assistant Property Management with 5+ years of experience seeking new opportunities where my customer service background and education can be utilized to the fullest, providing customers with the highest quality of service and investors with a high rate of return on their investment. Hospitality Management Associate. Real Estate License in process. Personable, organized and task-oriented.

Experience



1170 Apartment Corp

Assistant Property Manager New Jersey, United States

- *Help manage 26 Buildings for a total of 1170 units in a 35 acres land
- *Advertise units and negotiate lease terms
- *Perform tenant screenings
- *Experience with Yardi, Outlook, Excel and Microsoft Word
- *Act as liaison between tenants and property owners
- *Responsible for implementing lease renewal
- *Collect rent on a monthly basis and handle late payments in a timely manner
- *Maintain property by addressing tenant complaints, completing repairs, occupancy
- *Coordinate maintenance schedule with Maintenance Coordinator
- *Create, mentor and manage a cohesive property maintenance team

Smart Realty

Jan 2019-Present(1 years, 6 months)

O Jan 2016 - Present

(4 years, 6 months)

Property Sales Consultant / Leasing Specialist

New Jersey, United States

- *Generating leads and turning them into opportunities for sales and rentals
- *Contacting potential customers via telephone & email
- *Arranging meetings with prospects in order to tour property
- *Front office customer service
- *Preparing lease documentation, property inspections, completing move-in and out paperwork and procedures

Education



Real Estate

O Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

Kovats Real Estate School

Associate's Degree

O Dec 2010-Jan 2014

Hospitality Administration / Management

Bergen Community College

- *Overseeing personnel, ensuring that the facilities are properly maintained, taking steps to ensure customer satisfaction and overseeing the upkeep of administrative and financial records.
- *Accounting
- *Economics
- *Marketing, and human resource management.
- *Safety and health prevention norms.